A Finding Aid to the Charles Rand Penney Papers, 1923-1994, bulk 1945-1994, in the Archives of American Art AAA.pennchar
Archives of American Art
- Art Collection Files, 1923-1994; Series 1; 22.7 Linear feet Boxes 1-23, OV 24
  - Davis, Stuart (Box 6)
    - Works Progress Administration, circa 1980-1987 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - De Creeft, Jose, General, 1959-1989 (Box 6, Folder 34-35)
  - De Creeft, Jose, Storm King Art Center, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Dehn, Adolf, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - De Saint Phalle, Niki, 1970-1993 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Delaunay, Sonia, 1970-1989 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Diao, David, 1975-1993 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Dobkin, Alexander, 1968-1980 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Dohanos, Stevan, 1964-1986 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Dorazio, Piero, 1969-1981 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Du Buffet, Jean, 1973-1993 (Box 6, Folder 44-45)
  - Du Champ, Marcel (Box 6)
    - General, 1968-1994 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Du Champ, Marcel (Box 7)
    - Anne D'Harnoncourt, 1975-1987 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Coachman on Box (1904-1905), 1972-1986 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Death of the Artist, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Philadelphia Museum of Art, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Relief Sculpture, 1968-1981 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Dwight, Mabel, 1972-1984 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Eichenberg, Fritz, General, 1980-1984 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Eichenberg, Fritz, Death of the Artist, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Eilshemius, Louis, 1960-1993 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Ernst, Jimmy, 1970-1989 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Ernst, Max, General, 1968-1992 (Box 7, Folder 11-12)
  - Ernst, Max, Lithographs, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Etrog, Sorel (Box 7)
    - General, 1969-1988 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Book and Print, circa 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Dominion Gallery, 1967-1972 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Dunkelman Gallery, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Felix Landau Gallery, 1965-1968 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Gallery Moos Limited, 1967-1984 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - In the Shadow II, 1971-1989 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - J.L. Hudson Gallery, circa 1968 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Marlborough Godard Gallery, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Rose Fried Gallery, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Staempfli Gallery, 1968-1977 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Toronto Symphony, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Evergood, Philip (Box 7)
    - General, 1963-1992 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - ACA Galleries, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Associated American Artists, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Bernard Danenberg Galleries, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Gallery 63, Inc., 1963-1965 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - The Graphic Work, Book by Lucy R. Lippard, circa 1966 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Head of a Young Man (1950), 1964-1987 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Kendall Taylor, 1985-1988 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Kennedy Galleries, 1970-1988 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Letter to the Editor and Death of the Artist, 1965-1973 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Mother and Child (1949), 1963-1988 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - "Never Separate from the Heart" (1986), 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Open Letter to Evergood from Alexander Eliot, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Terry Dintenfass, Inc., 1974-1994 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Vatican Gallery of Modern Art, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Farr, Helen, 1973-1985 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Feininger, Lyonel, 1971-1988 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Ferber, Hubert, General, 1970-1991 (Box 7, Folder 45-46)
  - Ferber, Hubert, Storm King Art Center, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Fiene, Ernest, 1972-1994 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Filipovic, Augustin, 1965-1973 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Fink, Bruce, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Finn, David, 1971-1977 (Box 7, Folder 51-52)
  - Finn, David, 1978-1993 (Box 8, Folder 1-4)
  - Flagg, James Montgomery (Box 8)
    - General, 1972-1994 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Boys and Girls You Can Help Your Uncle Sam Win the War Poster, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - G.K. Chesterton (1972), Purchase, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - I Want You for U.S. Army Poster, 1972-1985 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Flannagan, John B., 1968-1987 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Ford, Marian, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Francis, Sam, 1969-1994 (Box 8, Folder 11-12)
  - Frasconi, Antonio, 1964-1992 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - French, Daniel Chester, 1968-1992 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Fuller, R. Buckminster (Box 8)
    - General, 1967-1985 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Buffalo School of Architecture of Governmental Design Reception, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Dymaxion Air-Ocean World, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Single-Cell Jitterbug (1976), 1976-1981 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Furst, Donald, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Ganso, Emil (Box 8)
    - General, 1963-1972 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Associated American Artists, 1963-1967 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Biographical Information, undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Cleveland Museum of Art, circa 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Framing, 1969-1979 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Galerie Sumers, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Hubert Palmer Gallery, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Kenan Center Exhibition, Catalogue, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Kenan Center Exhibition, Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Kenan Center Exhibition, Framing, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Kenan Center Exhibition, General, circa 1969 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Kenan Center Exhibition, Invitation, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Kenan Center Exhibition, Publicity, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Kenan Center Exhibition, Speech Given by Charles Rand Penney, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Letter to John Pirog from Penney, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Martin Sumers Graphics, 1978-1982 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Memorial Art Gallery, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Ohio Collector in New York Times, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Pitcher and Peaches (1963), Purchase, 1963-1967 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Research File, General, 1977-1994 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Research File, Brooklyn Museum, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Research File, Cleveland Museum of Art, circa 1964 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Ganso, Emil (Box 9)
    - Research File, Joann Moser, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Research File, Leonard Bocour, 1965-1973 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Research File, Library of Congress, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Research File, Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Research File, Museum of Modern Art, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Research File, New York City Public Library, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Research File, Philadelphia Museum of Art, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Research File, References, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Spring (1963), Gift to Roberson Memorial Center, 1980-1989 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - University of Iowa Exhibition, 1965-1982 (Box 9, Folder 10-11)
    - University of Iowa Exhibition, 1965-1982 (Box 9, Folder 12-13)
    - University of Iowa Exhibition, Publicity, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - University of Iowa Exhibition Catalog, The Graphic Art of Emil Ganso (1979), 1980-1992 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - University of Iowa, Gift of 36 Artworks by Penney, 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Vernon L. Bobbitt at Albion College, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - William Benton Museum of Art, University of Connecticut, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Gedeohn, Paul, 1966-1975 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Giacometti, Alberto, 1966-1988 (Box 9, Folder 20-21)
  - Giacometti, Diego, 1967-1992 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Gilhooly, David, 1975-1982 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Gillespie, Dorothy, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Gladstone, Gerald (Box 9)
    - General, 1966-1976 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Barbara Regen Gladstone, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Biographical Information, 1966-1981 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Dorothy Cameron, 1965-1967 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Dunkelman Gallery, 1967-1970 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - "Fifteen Canadian Artists" (1963) (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - High Park, Toronto "Sculpt-In" (1967) (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Image of Print, undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Sheila Gladstone, Wife, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Space (1961-1962), 1963-1966 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Space Drawing I (1961), 1965 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Universal Man (1976) (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Goodnough, Robert (Box 9)
    - General, 1974-1982 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - ACA Galleries, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Andre Emmerich Gallery, 1972-1982 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Artworks in the Charles Rand Penney Collection, General, 1976-1984 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Artworks in the Charles Rand Penney Collection, Abstraction in Black and Red (1962), 1965-1980 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Artworks in the Charles Rand Penney Collection, Abstraction X (1963), 1963-1980 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Artworks in the Charles Rand Penney Collection, Black Boat Drawing (1964), 1965-1980 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Artworks in the Charles Rand Penney Collection, The Boat, 1963-1980 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Artworks in the Charles Rand Penney Collection, Primary Blocks (1965), 1965-1980 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Artworks in the Charles Rand Penney Collection, Red and Blue Forms (1964), 1965-1980 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Biographical Information, 1961-1972 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Correspondence from Penney to Goodnough, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - David Mirvish Gallery, 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Dr. Martin Harry Bush at Wichita State University, 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Everson Museum, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - G Contemporary Paintings and James Goodman Gallery, 1961-1965 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Interview in Arts Magazine by Matthew Rose, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Goodnough, Robert (Box 10)
    - John Bernard Myers, 1971-1987 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Kennedy Graphics, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Knoedler Contemporary Art, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - "New Paintings" (1980) (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Nina Freudenheim Gallery, 1978-1983 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Photographic Materials, circa 1960s (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Publicity, 1962-1987 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Shipee Gallery, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Tibor de Nagy Gallery, 1960-1990 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Gorky, Arshile, 1962-1981 (Box 10, Folder 10-11)
  - Gottshall, David, circa 1980s (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Gottshall, Marie, circa 1980s (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Graves, Morris (Box 10)
    - General, 1955-1994 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Bird of the Inner Eye (1935), 1977 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - "Morris Graves: Vision of the Inner Eye" (1983), 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - "Reconciling Inner and Outer Realities" (1992), Traveling Museum Show, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Schmidt Bingham Gallery, 1992-1994 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Graves, Nancy Stevenson, 1980-1980 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Greco, Emilio, 1970-1986 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Greenwood, Marion, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Grooms, Red (Box 10)
    - General, 1972-1992 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1960s (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - The Bookstore (1979), 1978-1980 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Chicago, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Discount Store, 1970-1973 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Farmer and Cow (1968), 1969-1989 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Creative Time, Inc., 1981-1987 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Films, 1980-1984 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - John Bernard Myers Gallery, 1971-1987 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Marlborough Gallery, Inc., 1979-1992 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Nan Miller Gallery, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Periodical, Art News, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Periodical, Portfolio, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Poster Advertisements, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Prints, 1971-1986 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - "Red Grooms: A Retrospective 1956-1984" (1985-1987) (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Red Grooms, Book by Carter Ratcliff, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Ruckus Manhattan (1975), 1975-1986 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Tibor de Nagy Gallery, 1969-1990 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art Exhibition (1987) (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Grosz, George, 1969-1989 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Hadzi, Dimitri (Box 10)
    - General, 1978-1990 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Gruenebaum Gallery, 1979-1986 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Kouros Gallery, 1988-1991 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Martin Sumers Graphics, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - National Institute of Arts and Letters Grant, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Omphalos, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Pillars of Hercules III (1977), 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Stephen Radich Gallery, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Halaby, Samia A., 1976-1985 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Harpignies, Henri Joseph, 1962-1994 (Box 10, Folder 52-53)
  - Hastenteufel, Dieter, General, 1979-1985 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Hastenteufel, Dieter, It's Only In Your Mind, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Hayter, Stanley William, 1980-1993 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Herbert, Al, 1965-1980 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Henri, Robert, 1962-1994 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Hepworth, Barbara (Box 11)
    - General, 1970-1985 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Carborundum 1977 Award for Excellence (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Columbus Museum of Art, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Death of the Artist, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Kenan Center, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Oblique Forms (1969), 1970 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Porthmeor (1969), circa 1969 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Post Cards, circa 1970s (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Syon Park, London, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Twelve Lithographs (1969), circa 1969 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Variation of a Theme (1958), 1970-1976 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Various Galleries, 1969-1982 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Honegger, Gottfried, 1964-1972 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Hopper, Edward (Box 11)
    - General, 1967-1986 (Box 11, Folder 20-21)
    - "The Art and the Artist" (1980-1982), Chicago Stock Exchange Trading Room, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - "The Art and the Artist" (1980-1982), Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - "The Art and the Artist" (1980-1982), Publicity, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - "The Art and the Artist" (1980-1982), San Francisco Museum of Modern Art, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - "The Art and the Artist" (1980-1982), Whitney Museum of American Art, 1980-1983 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - "Edward Hopper: Prints and Illustrations" (1979), Preview Dinner (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - "Edward Hopper: Selections from the Permanent Collection" (1989) (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Hirschl and Adler Galleries, 1987-1994 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Hopper's Places, Book by Gail Levin, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Hopper Symposium, 1980-1983 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Kennedy Galleries, 1987-1989 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Night Shadows (1921), 1964-1994 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Nude, 1972-1994 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Post Cards, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Prints, 1979-1987 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Smash the Hun (1918), 1972-1994 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Hopper, Edward (Box 12)
    - Smash the Hun (1918), 1972-1994 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Smash the Hun (1918), Addison-Wesley Publishing, 1982-1994 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Smash the Hun (1918), Bonfini Press, 1983-1985 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Smash the Hun (1918), Hazan Editions, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Smash the Hun (1918), Holt, Rinehart, and Winston, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Studio, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Susan Sheehan, Inc., 1988 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art Permanent Collection, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Hornaday, Richard, 1962-1985 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Hurd, Peter, 1964-1992 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Hurtubise, Jacques, 1965-1988 (Box 12, Folder 11-12)
  - John, Augustus, 1970-1982 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Johns, Jasper, 1977-1992 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Jenkins, Paul (Box 12)
    - General, 1962-1983 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Associated American Artists, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Biographical Information, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Gallery Moos Limited, 1963-1968 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Gimpel Fils, Gimpel and Weitzenhoffer, 1978-1985 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Martha Jackson Gallery, 1958-1991 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Phenomena with Kamlot (1961), 1962-1991 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Kahn, Wolf, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Katz, Alex, 1968-1986 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Keller, Henry G. (Box 12)
    - General, circa 1976-1994 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Albert Keller, Son, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1960s (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - "Birchfield and His Teacher, Henry G. Keller" (1973) (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Black Mesa, New Mexico, circa 1964 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Boyhood Memories (1934), circa 1960s (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Flower Fantasy (1932), circa 1960s (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - "The Henry G. Keller Memorial Exhibition" (1950), 1950-1968 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Hungry Plow Horses No. 1 (1935), circa 1960s (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Letter from Keller to Leona Prasse in 1949, circa 1970 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Old Fashioned Bouquet, circa 1960s (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Paul H. Oppmann, Nephew, 1968-1970 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Pelican Rookery No. 1 (1938), circa 1960s (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Pelican Rookery No. 2 (1938), circa 1960s (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Surprise or Cock in the Garden (1932), circa 1960s (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Vixseboxse Art Galleries, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - The Wreck, circa 1964 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Kent, Rockwell, 1971-1993 (Box 12, Folder 41-42)
  - King, William Dickey, General, 1971-1994 (Box 12, Folder 43-44)
  - King, William Dickey, Storm King Art Center, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Kiningstein, Jonah, 1961-1993 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Kipp, Lyman, General, 1971-1991 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Kipp, Lyman, Storm King Art Center, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Kitaj, Ronald B., 1970-1994 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Klein, Richard, 1965-1973 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Kline, Franz, 1965-1992 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Kohn, Gabriel, 1960-1991 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Kroll, Leon, 1984-1994 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Kuhn, Walt, 1967-1971 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Kuniyoshi, Yasuo, General, 1963-1989 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Kuniyoshi, Yasuo, Catalogue Raisonne, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Laboureur, Jean-Emile, 1964-1981 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Lachaise, Gaston, 1963-1992 (Box 13, Folder 13-14)
  - Lamis, Leroy, 1963-1975 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Landeck, Armin, 1977-1986 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Lasansky, Mauricio, 1971-1988 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Leger, Fernand, 1965-1989 (Box 13, Folder 18-19)
  - Levine, Jack, General, 1970-1988 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Levine, Jack, Midtown Payson Galleries, Inc., 1990 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Liberman, Alexander, General, 1970-1992 (Box 13, Folder 22-23)
  - Liberman, Alexander, Storm King Art Center, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1965-1991 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1965-1991 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Linder, Richard, 1970-1986 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Lipton, Seymour, General, 1970-1989 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Lipton, Seymour, Storm King Art Center, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Longo, Vincent, 1970-1987 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Lozowick, Louis, 1972-1992 (Box 14, Folder 6-7)
  - Lubbers, Adriaan, circa 1977-1980 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Luks, George (Box 14)
    - General, 1972-1988 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Cape Eliza, Maine (1922), General, 1962-1992 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Cape Eliza, Maine (1922), Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Childs Gallery, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - David Findlay, Jr., 1991 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Edward W. Root, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Kraushaar Galleries, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Man, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Memorial Art Gallery, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Macri, Giuseppe, 1961-1978 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Magritte, Rene (Box 14)
    - General, 1967-1992 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Homme au Chapeau [Man with Hat], 1968-1972 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - L'Envolee [Flight], 1968-1980 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Maillol, Aristede, 1970-1982 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Manolo, Manuel M.H., 1964-1983 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Manship, Paul, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Manzu, Giacomo (Box 14)
    - General, 1979-1986 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Busto de Donna (1937), 1967-1986 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Death of the Artist, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Paul Rosenberg and Co., 1965-1985 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Tasende Gallery, 1979-1987 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Weintraub Gallery, 1980-1986 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Wildenstein Gallery, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Marca-Relli, Conrad, 1970-1990 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Marcks, Gerhard, General, 1977-1993 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Marcks, Gerhard, Storm King Art Center, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Marin, John (Box 14)
    - General, 1960-1991 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1977-1988 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Archives of American Art, 1960-1961 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Catalogue Raisonne, 1963-1985 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Coe Kerr Gallery, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - The Downtown Gallery, 1963-1965 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Edith Gregor Halpert, 1965-1984 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Films, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Green and Red Motif (1922) and Downtown New York (1921), Purchase, 1963-1965 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - J. Benjamin Townsend, Comments for Studio Arena Theater, circa 1960s (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Kennedy Galleries, 1981-1990 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Marlborough Gallery, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - National Gallery of Art, Gift of Pictures and Sketchbooks by John Mann, Jr., 1986 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Oils, Parrish Art Museum and Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - The Phillips Collection, 1967-1981 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Weyhe Gallery, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1964-1971 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Willard Gallery, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Marini, Marino, 1967-1991 (Box 14, Folder 53-54)
  - Marsh, Reginald (Box 15)
    - General, 1962-1988 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Associated American Artists, 1970-1982 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Bernard Danenberg Galleries, Inc., 1971 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Bowery Scene (1945), 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Coney Island Beach, 1964-1980 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Frank Rehn Gallery, 1964-1973 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Hirschl and Adler Galleries, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Kennedy Galleries, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Lloyd Goodrich, 1972-1976 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Martin Gordon Gallery, 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Memorial Art Gallery, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Sid Deutsch Gallery, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Switch Engines, Erie Yards, Jersey City, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Ten Female Nudes, 1967-1988 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Twelve Female Nudes, 1967-1988 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1967-1983 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - William Benton, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Wonderland (1943), 1970-1973 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Massey, Ralph A., 1976-1994 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Matta, Roberto Echaurren, 1970-1993 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Matulka, Jan, 1980-1992 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Meadows, Bernard (Box 15)
    - General, 1963-1985 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Abstract Bird, 1964-1984 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1976 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Cock, 1963-1984 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Miki, Tomio, 1965-1986 (Box 15, Folder 27-28)
  - Miller, Kenneth Hays, 1978-1987 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Miro, Joan (Box 15)
    - General, 1979-1989 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Acquavella Galleries, Inc., 1982 (Box 15, Folder 31)